
let all_questions = [
  {
    question: "I can't find my wallet (...).",
    answers: ["everywhere","anywhere","nobody"],
    correct: "anywhere"
  },
  {
    question: "I would be the best runner in the world if I (...) both legs.",
    answers: ["have","lost","had"],
    correct: "were"
  },
  {
    question: "Why did you (...) my soup?",
    answers: ["eat","ate","eaten"],
    correct: "eat"
  },
  {
    question: "He can't use a computer. He shouldn't be (...).",
    answers: ["a technician","an actress","a waiter"],
    correct: "a technician"
  },
  {
    question: "Gregory got the sack yesterday. Now, he's (...), because he hated his job.",
    answers: ["satisfied","ashamed","annoyed"],
    correct: "satisfied"
  },
  {
    question: "Jerry felt absolutely crushed when he saw his house (...) by Rick.",
    answers: ["destroyed","destroying","destroy"],
    correct: "destroyed"
  },
  {
    question: "She (...) there since 2003.",
    answers: ["live","has lived","lives"],
    correct: "has lived"
  },
  {
    question: "I don't like living on a housing estate. I prefer living in a (...) in the countryside.",
    answers: ["terraced house","block of flats","cottage"],
    correct: "cottage"
  },
  {
    question: "Warum ist diese Frage hier?.",
    answers: ["Ich weiß nicht.","Nie wiem.","I don't know."],
    correct: "Ich weiß nicht."
  },
  {
    question: "Bill Gates became interested in computers (...) he was a child.",
    answers: ["when","during","after"],
    correct: "when"
  },
  {
    question: "I don't earn money because I am (...).",
    answers: ["employed","unemployed","self-employed"],
    correct: "unemployed"
  },
  {
    question: "If you don't water plants, they (...).",
    answers: ["would die","die","had died"],
    correct: "die"
  },
  {
    question: "My favourite (...) is Claude Monet.",
    answers: ["artist","art","artistic"],
    correct: "artist"
  },
  {
    question: "This is the canteen (...) we eat our lunch.",
    answers: ["that","which","where"],
    correct: "where"
  },
  {
    question: "The room was cosy with (...) stairs leading up to the next floor.",
    answers: ["wood","wooden","woolen"],
    correct: "wooden"
  },
  {
    question: "You're not (...) to watch X-rated films. You have to be 18.",
    answers: ["old enough","enough old","too old"],
    correct: "old enough"
  },
  {
    question: "Oh, a misery! (...) wants to be my enemy.",
    answers: ["Everybody","Anybody","Everywhere"],
    correct: "Everybody"
  },
  {
    question: "Grace finds her new job interesting but (...).",
    answers: ["demand","demanded","demanding"],
    correct: "demanding"
  },
  {
    question: "Choose a (...) you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life.",
    answers: ["work","job","working"],
    correct: "job"
  },
  {
    question: "You need a university degree to (...) for this job.",
    answers: ["apply","resign","work"],
    correct: "apply"
  },
  {
    question: "There isn't (...) to see here.",
    answers: ["anything","nothing","something"],
    correct: "anything"
  },
  {
    question: "If you were me, you (...) all hopes.",
    answers: ["would lose","losen","lose"],
    correct: "would lose"
  },
  {
    question: "The Eiffel Tower is probably the most popular tourist (...) in Paris.",
    answers: ["attract","attraction","attractive"],
    correct: "attraction"
  },
  {
    question: "When I got home yesterday, my mum had (...) dinner.",
    answers: ["make","did","made"],
    correct: "made"
  },
  {
    question: "My dad has lived in our house (...) he was born.",
    answers: ["for","since","just"],
    correct: "since"
  },
  {
    question: `Why do you say incorrectly "(...)" instead of saying "ducks".`,
    answers: ["docks","duck","ducks"],
    correct: "docks"
  },
  {
    question: "You really shouldn't spend (...) much time playing games.",
    answers: ["so","such","enough"],
    correct: "so"
  },
  {
    question: "Text me (...) you get home tonight, OK?",
    answers: ["after","until","during"],
    correct: "after"
  },
  {
    question: "How (...) eggs did you buy?",
    answers: ["many","much","more"],
    correct: "so"
  },
  {
    question: "If I were you, I (...) more.",
    answers: ["will train","trained","would train"],
    correct: "would train"
  }
];
